Tourists are popular targets for pickpockets.
The existence of pickpockets in a crowded tourist spot
is a threat to the people gathered there.
That threat applies to everyone in the vicinity, even other pickpockets,
if you are in the vicinity, and a pickpocket has identified you as a target.
You are facing a threat actor
whether you know it or not,
the approach and technique taken by the pickpocket is their threat vector.
Let's say the pickpocket chooses you as a target
because they see that it will be easier or more profitable to steal from you.
Maybe you are distracted have jewelry that is easy to snatch
or appear weak and less likely to put up a struggle.
In other words, you appear more vulnerable than the other tourists
and the pickpocket feels that they can exploit that vulnerability or weakness.